跟随押送人员  打开一号门
快走
打开二号门
走吧  面对墙壁   跟着押送人员
-早上好 -早上好
-Good morning. -Morning.
-请报上你的名字 -丹尼欧森
-State your name for the record. -Daniel Ocean.
谢谢  欧森先生   这次听证会我们想确认
Thank you. The purpose of this hearing is to determine...
...你是否会想再次触犯法律
...whether you are likely to break the law again.
虽然这是你初次被定罪
This was your first conviction,but you were implicated...
但你曾涉及与众多案件的策划有关
...in a dozen other schemesand frauds.
对此你有什么愿对我们说的?
What can you tell us about this?
如你所说  女士  之前我都是清白的
As you say, ma'am,I was never charged.
欧森先生  我们想要知道的是
We're trying to find out...
这次犯罪你的动机是什么...
...if there was a reason for committing this crime...
或者说你被逮捕的原因是什么
...or just a reason you got caught this time.
妻子离开了我  这让我很伤心
My wife left me. I was upset.
于是才做下了这种自我毁灭的行径
I got into a self-destructive pattern.
若被释放  你还会 再做出同样的行为吗?
If released, is it likely you'd fall back into a similar pattern?
她已经离开了我   不会再有同样的事发生
She left me once. I doubt she'd do it again just for kicks.
欧森先生   若被释放后你有何打算?
Mr.Ocean, what do you thinkyou would do if released?
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 修正调整
欢迎爱好者加入我们 www. YYeTs. com
字幕来源: 网络     后期:beenoera
罗汉
十一
十一罗汉
-给我换点筹码 -好
-Chips, please. -Sure.
新泽西州  大西洋城
换150块  要十五分的还要五分的?
-Change 1 50. Quarters or nickels?
五分的吧
-Quarters are fine.
-祝你好运 -谢谢
-Good luck. -Thank you.
20  庄家19 开局不错
Twenty. Dealer has 19. Good start.
-我要休息了 -非常感谢
-I'm going on break now. -Here. Thank you very much.
-祝你好运 -好好休息
-Good luck. -You have a good one.
-你好吗  先生?  -你好  弗兰克
-How are you, sir? -Hello, Frank.
抱歉  先生 你一定是把我和别人搞混了
I beg your pardon. You must have me confused with someone else.
我叫拉蒙  铭牌上写着的
My name is Ramon. As you can see right here.
-对不起 -没关系
-My mistake. -No problem, sir.
这台子很冷清啊
The table's cold anyway.
你可以先在凯撒皇宫里到处逛逛
You might want to try the loungeat Caesars.
这儿到了一点就热闹了
Gets busy after 1 :00.
-一点?  -是的  先生
-1 :00? -Yes, sir.
谢谢  拉蒙
Thanks, Ramon.
谢谢
Thank you.
拉斯维加斯的里程碑将被夷为平地   前赌场业主放弃营业
-在关心什么新闻?  -拉蒙
-Checking up on current events? -Ramon.
很高兴遇到你   弗兰克卡顿是不会出现在赌桌前的
Glad to meet you. Frank Catton can't get past the gaming board.
-刚出来?  -今天下午出来的
-You just got out? -This afternoon.
和他有联系吗?
You seen him?
听说他在教某位电影明星如何玩牌 怎么了?
I heard he was teaching movie star show to play cards. Why?
又有计划了?
You have a plan already?
开什么玩笑 我才刚成为正常人
Are you kidding? I just became a citizen again.
布罗克长官...
Officer Brooks...
...我是丹尼欧森 我被告知要与你24小时保持联系
...this is Danny Ocean. I was told to contact you within 24 hours.
不是  我没有遇到麻烦
No, sir, I haven't been getting in trouble.
不是  我没有酗酒
No, sir, I haven't been drinking.
不是  我也不想离开这国家
No, sir, I wouldn't even think about leaving the state.
加里福尼亚州好莱坞
嗨  拉斯! 拉斯提 怎么样  兄弟?
Hey, Russ! Rusty. What's up, man?
我就这么问你吧   打算入伙吗?
Let me ask you a question. Are you incorporated?
你该考虑下  我和我经济人说过了...
You should think about it. I talked to my manager--
-伯尼?  -不是那个伯尼  是生意上的经济人
-Bernie? -Not Bernie. My business manager.
不过他们倒都是叫伯尼
Actually, they' re both named Bernie.
他说我们做的事 在将来可能会被调查
He said what we do could be considered research...
...所以我必须在财务上做好帐
...for a future gig, so I could make it a tax write-off.
关键是问题全出在他身上 那简直蠢透了
The one thing is, and this is his thing and it's stupid...
...可我只有用支票付你工资了
...but I'd have to pay you by check.
或者我们可以拿现金
Or we could just stick to cash.
对  那就拿现金
Yeah, let's just stick to cash.
先玩五张牌   大家都还记得玩法吗?
We'll begin with five-card draw. Everyone remember that?
谁愿意来发牌? 乔希?
Who wants to start us out? Josh?
乔希  你该往左发牌
Josh. To the left.
发牌要从左边开始
Deal to your left.
-谢恩?  -加张牌
-Shane? -Hit me.
-这可不是玩21点 -假正经!
-It's not blackjack. -Dude!
只需要看着牌  不需要换
Looking at them doesn't change them.
你只需清楚自己是什么牌就可
You know what you have.
-左边  左边 -左边  我知道
-Left. Left. -Left, I'll get it.
女士下注  开始吧
Lady bets. Let's keep it moving.
-蓝筹码 -蓝筹码  那是五十块的
-Blue. -Blue, that's a 50.
-我可以叫吗?  -可以
-I'll call? -Okay.
谢恩叫五十
Shane's calling. 50.
搞什么  弄的那么严肃
What the hell, it's only pocket change.
你只管押注吧   假装这是大赌局
Betting's your business. Pretend it's for a reason.
好  谢谢  伙计
Yeah, thanks, man.
-是的 -多少?
-Right. -How many?
-四 -你不能叫四  你应该退出
-Four. -You don't want four. You wanna fold.
-我不该跟牌?  -是的
-I wanna fold? -Fold.
那样可以吗?
Is that good?
你完蛋了  放下牌吧 你完蛋了
You're done. Let's take that. You're done.
你完蛋了  你手上有三对
You're done. You have three pairs.
五张牌的游戏  你手上却有六张
You can't have six cardsin a five-card game.
-也许有张牌是我的 -不是发牌上的错
-Maybe one was mine. -Wasn't me.
大家安静!
Fellas!
全红
All reds.
怎么样  伙计?
What up, dog?
我很乐意花你们的钱 我得把车洗一遍
I'm gonna love spending your money. I'm gonna get my car washed.
-玩的怎么样?  -无聊透了
-How's the game going? -Longest hour of my life.
-什么?  -我打算带你妻子私奔
-What? -I'm running away with your wife.
很好
Great.
从电视工作转到电影拍摄难吗?
Isn't that hard, crossing over from television to film?
对我来说不怎么难
Not for me, dude.
拉斯  我们又找到位
Hey, Russ. We got another player...
...和你一样棒的牌手
...if that's cool with you.
不介意我这么问的话   请问您是做什么的?
What do you do for a living? If you don't mind me asking.
我为何要介意?
Why would I mind you asking?
两张牌
Two cards.
我刚从牢里出来
I just got out of prison.
-真的吗?  -怎么进去的?
-Really? -Why were you in prison?
偷窃罪
I stole things.
偷窃? 偷珠宝吗?
You stole things? Like jewels?
印加婚礼面具
Incan matrimonial head masks.
那印加什么的值钱吗...?
-Any money in lncan matrimonial--?
是面具  值那么点钱吧
-Head masks. Some.
别听他胡说  那值的钱令你搬不动
Don't let him fool you. There's loads if you can move them.
-我办的到的你就办不到 -我的销赃人很可靠
-I'll take one. But you can't. -My fence seemed confident.
-若直接拿现金根本不需要销赃人 -缺乏远见
-With cash you don't need a fence. -Some lack vision.
只有被关在囚室中的人才会如此
Probably everybody in cell block E.
押五百
That's $500.
-赌局上的第一堂课是什么?  -永远别赌...
-What's the first lesson in poker? -Never bet on the--
-要把个人情绪摒之门外 -对
-No, leave emotion at the door. -Right.
今天的课是: 如何使诈
Today's lesson: How to draw out the bluff.
这赌局已经累积了很多的钱
That much money early in the game....
他的牌不可能比一对花牌更好
He has nothing better than a pair of face cards.
巴里?
Barry?
好
All right.
我不跟
I fold.
-乔希?  -别担心  我跟
-Josh? -Don't worry, I'm game.
我跟你500  然后再...
I will see your $500 and I will raise you another...
-...大你五百 -押的很漂亮
-...$500 of my own. -That's a very handsome bet.
不过小心  别把它推的太高太快
Careful, don't push him too high,too fast.
将那控制在一定范围内
I Keep him on the leash.
-荷莉?  -我跟
-Holly? -Call.
跟
Call.
我也跟
And I'll call.
跟500  再大你2000
I'll see your $500 and raise you $2000.
伙计们  现在你们该满意了 桌上的钱现在可有不少
Guys, you do what you like. That's a lot of money.
我会跟下去  他不过是在虚张声势
I'm staying in. He's trying to buy his way out of his bluff.
-乔希?  -两千
-Josh? -Two.
女孩也跟
Thattagirl. Call.
-跟 -跟
-Call. -Call.
开牌吧
Let's see them.
不知道四条九够不够大 不过算上张A那就很大了
I'm not sure what four nines does, but the ace, I think, is pretty high.
真是让我们大开眼界
Thanks for the tip on bluffing.
托菲! 给我们签个名怎么样?  来吧  很快的
Hey, Topher! How about an autograph? Come on, real quick.
-天  我无聊死了 -你看起来就很无聊
-God, I'm bored. -You look bored.
牢里的日子怎么样?  收到我寄的饼干了吗?
How was the clink? You get the cookies I sent?
为什么还要我来找你?
Why do you think I came to see you first?
-告诉我有什么计划 -这活很复杂
-So tell me. -It's tricky.
之前从未被做过 需要很好的计划和众多的参与者
It's never been done before. It'll need planning and a large crew.
-要用到枪吗?  -不完全是  高度安全
-Guns? -Not quite. High security. The take--
-目标呢?  -有八个
-The target? -Eight figures.
具体是什么?
What's the target?
你上次去赌城是什么时候的事了?
When was the last time you were in Vegas?
你想去打劫赌场?
You want to knock over a casino?
这是美丽湖大酒店金库的平面图
The vault at the Bellagio.
如果我看的没错  我想说...
If I'm reading this right, and I'd like to think I am...
这是我所见过最复杂的金库
...this is probably the least accessible vault ever designed.
你说有三个赌场?
You said three casinos?
还有蜃楼酒店和米高梅大酒店 的钱也全放在这儿
These feed into the Mirage and MGMGrand, but every dime ends up there.
美丽湖酒店和蜃楼酒店
The Bellagio and the Mirage.
-那都是特瑞本尼迪克特的地盘 -对  没错
-These are Terry Benedict's places. -Yes, they are.
-他会介意吗?  -可能不止会介意
-Think he'll mind? -More than somewhat.
至少要集上12个人才能办成这事
You'd need at least 12 guys doing a combination of cons.
你觉得该找些什么人?
Like what, you think?
我仔细想过了
Off the top of my head,
我说你得 去找位波斯基  一位吉姆布朗
I'd say you're looking at a Boesky, a Jim Brown...
...一位戴茜小姐 还要一位莱昂斯平克斯
...a Miss Daisy and a Leon Spinks.
还需要埃拉菲兹杰拉德式的大人物
Not to mention the biggest Ella Fitzgerald ever.
搞到的钱请的起这些人吗?
Where will you get the money to back this?
要是计划成功   我们就搞的到那笔钱
Hit these three casinos, we'll get our bankroll.
本尼迪克特树敌众多
Benedict's got a list of enemies.
那些敌人难道输了地盘就没钱了?
But enemies with loose cash and nothing to lose?
-鲁宾 -鲁宾
-Reuben. -Reuben.
嘿
Hey.
奥斯卡  照低点行吗?
Oscar, lower it a bit, would you?
抱歉  完事了吗?  找到想要的东西没?
Sorry. You guys done? Find what you want?
我们正准备拿回家去做拷贝
We'll take these for the night to make copies.
-随便拿吧 -非常感谢
-Whatever you need. -Appreciate it.
怎么了?
What?
我需要理由
I need a reason.
别和我说是为了钱   你为什么这么做?
And don't say money. Why do this?
我为什么就不能做?
Why not do it?
在浪费了四年大好光阴之后 我刚从牢里被放出来
I just left the joint after losing four years of my life...
...而你也没把自己 的本事用在刀刃上
...and you're cold-decking Teen Beat cover boys.
因为总是赌场在赢钱
Because the house always wins.
要是玩久了   赌场会把你的人都吃了
Play long enough,the house takes you.
至少你要在手气好的时候多押几注
Unless, when that perfect hand comes,you bet big.
那样你才会赢庄家的钱
Then you take the house.
-这说辞你练习了多久?  -我有胡说吗?
-You practiced that speech? -Did I rush it?
好了  不过说我 无所事事也过分了点
It was good. The Teen Beat thing was harsh.
我在想鲁宾会怎么说
I wonder what Reuben will say.
你们简直是疯了!
You're out of your damn minds!
内华达州拉斯维加斯
你们两个都烧昏了脑子!
You're both of you nuts!
我比谁都了解赌场的保安措施 那套东西都是我发明的
I know more about casino security than any man. I invented it.
那不可能被破坏
And it cannot be beaten.
那里有监视器  警卫   还有防盗锁
They got cameras and watchers,they got locks.
有计时器  金库
They got timers, vaults.
武装保安员的数量 足够打下整个巴黎来!
They got enough armedpersonnel to occupy Paris!
算了  这个例子举的不恰当
Okay, bad example.
谁都没有尝试过
It's never been tried.
已经有人试过   他们甚至几乎快成功了
It's been tried. A few guys even came close.
知道赌城最成功三个劫匪的故事吗?
You know the three most successful robberies in Vegas?
三号劫匪  该发个铜牌
Number three, the bronze medal.
那个铅笔头抢了锁住的钱箱
Pencil neck grabs a lockbox at the Horseshoe.
抓住那个穿套装的人!
Grab the guy in the suit!
他算是比之前任何人 都接近门口  只差两步
He got two steps closer to the door than anyone before.
不许抢钱!
Leave the money!
二号最成功劫匪:
Second most successful robbery:
71年在弗拉明戈赌场   这家伙在被人逮住前
The Flamingo in '71. This guy actually tasted fresh oxygen...
算是真正呼吸到了 赌场外的新鲜空气
...before they grabbed him.
当然  在接下来的三星期 他只能靠管子来呼吸
Of course, he was breathing out of a hose for the next three weeks.
该死的嬉皮士
Goddamn hippie.
最后是抢劫拉斯维加斯赌场
And the closest any man has ever come...
最成功的劫匪
...to robbing a Las Vegas casino...
那是87年   发生在凯撒皇宫酒店之外
...was outside of Caesars in '87.
他来到这里...
He came...
下手抢劫...
...he grabbed...
...最后他们把他干了
...they conquered.
我说过什么?  你们是专家  是一流的
But what am I saying? You guy sare pros. The best.
我清楚你们会把钱搞出赌场
I'm sure you can make it out of the casino.
不过我们还不能忘了
Of course, lest we forget...
就算是你们能出来 还是处在该死的沙漠中央!
...once you're out, you're still in the middle of the fucking desert!
你说的对 他说的对
You're right. He's right.
我们的胃口是大了点
Our eyes were bigger than our stomachs.
说的是啊  我们太自以为是了
-That's what it is. Ego.
对  等等  等等
-Yeah, blah, blah.
-感谢你的招待 -饭做的很好吃
-Thanks for lunch. -The nicoise was delicious.
-抱歉打搅你 -不过话说回来
-Sorry to bother you. -Look, we go way back...
...这事情上我算是欠你们的
...and I owe you from the thing with the guy.
-没关系 -我没放在心上
-Our pleasure. -I'd never been to Belize.
把你的地址留给多米尼克 我有些家居设备要送给你
Give Dominic your addresses. I got some furniture to send you.
恕我好奇   你们要打劫的是哪家赌场?
Just out of curiosity, which casinos did you geniuses pick to rob?
美丽湖  蜃楼  还有大米高梅
The Bellagio, the Mirage andthe MGM Grand.
那些都是特瑞本尼迪克特的赌场
Those are Terry Benedict's casinos.
-他说的对吗?  -没错观点
-Is that right? -That's right.
你们这些家伙...
You guys...
...你们和特瑞本尼迪克特 有什么过节?
...what do you got against Terry Benedict?
他和你有什么过节才是关键
What do you have against him, is the question.
他霸占了我的赌场   把我轰了出来
He torpedoed my casino. Muscled me out.
而下个月那里就要被炸掉
Now he's gonna blow it up next monthto make way for some monstrosity.
-我知道你们要做什么 -我们要做什么?
-I see what you're doing. -What are we doing?
若是要对特瑞本尼迪克特下手   最好听我几句话
If you're gonna steal from Terry Benedict, you better goddamn know.
道上本来有规矩   你对某人动手  他再回击你
This used to be civilized. You'd hit a guy, he'd whack you.
可是到本尼迪克特身上...
But Benedict....
说到底  最好别让他 知道是谁动的手
At the end of it, he'd better not know you're involved.
不然他就会将人赶至绝路
Because he'll kill you,then he'll go to work on you.
所以我们就需要非常小心   准备周全
That's why we have to bevery careful, very precise.
还需要一定的资金
Well-funded.
你也一定是疯了
You gotta be nuts too.
你们就需要象 你们一样疯狂的家伙
And you're gonna need a crew as nuts as you are.
你觉得谁比较适合呢?
Who do you got in mind?
-好  有谁加入?  -弗兰克已经进来了
-Alright, who 's in? -Frank C. is in.
弗兰克已经以支气管炎的理由
Frank has bronchitis and is applying
申请转到较暖和的地区工作
for a transfer to warmer climates.
开车的呢?
Drivers?
-我已经和麦罗伊兄弟谈过了 -摩门双胞胎?
-I talked to the Malloys. -Mormon twins?
他们现在在犹它州  没工作
They're in Utah, off the job.
最近正无聊的很
They're having trouble filling the hours.
-你先  亲爱的 -好了  一起出发
-Waiting, sweet heart. -Good. Go.
-等你先发车 -为什么?
-I'm waiting. -Why?
-你怎么象女人那么话多!  -轻松点
-You're a little girl! -Relax.
我会象揍法国佬那样好好教训你
I'm going to get out and drop you like third-period French.
轻松点
Relax.
加里福尼亚州洛杉矶
-电子专家呢?  -利文斯顿戴尔
-Electronics? -Livingston Dell.
他曾为FBI防暴组做监视
He 's been doing surveillance work for the FBI mob squad.
-胆量如何?  -还不坏
-How are his nerves? -Not so bad.
进去一点点
Move in a little bit.
-别  别碰那个 -为什么不行?
-Don't--Don't touch that. -Why not?
我有拿过你的枪   然后甩来甩去的吗?
Do you see me grabbing your gun and waving it around?
监视员  轻松点
Hey, RadioShack. Relax.
军需品呢?
Munitions.
-菲尔特伦丁 -他已经死了
-Phil Turrentine. -Dead.
-别胡扯  他还在干吗?  -他得了皮肤癌
-No shit. On the job? -Skin cancer.
-送花了吗?  -我约过他妻子
-You send flowers? -Dated his wife for a while.
巴舍就在这城里
Basher's in town.
应该可以派上点用处
There may be an issue with availability.
好了  准备...
All right, chaps...
小心短裤被震下来
...hang on to your knickers.
噢  别这样
Oh, leave it out!
你们这些笨蛋! 现在有麻烦了!
You tossers! You had one job to do!
你使用的家伙就只有这些?
That's all you used in the event?
-你是在唬我吗?  -是吗? 那又如何?
-You accusing me of booby-trapping? -Well?
泰尔先生从不唬人  是吗?
Booby traps aren't Mr.Tarr's style. Isn't that right?
巴舍?
Basher?
我是火器局的佩克
Peck. ATF.
让我猜猜你的手段
Let me venture a guess.
简单的G4ㄧ爆  20尺外引爆
Simple G-4 mainliner, back wound,quick fuse with a drag under 20 feet.
让我这么问你  你是要找这家伙吗?
Let me ask you this. You search this scumbag...
我是说  真正的找他
...for booby traps? I mean, really searched.
靠后
Stand back.
好了
Here we go.
-去找吉格斯  叫他过来 -谁?
-Find Griggs. I need him. -Who?
给我去找他来  听不懂吗?
Just find him, will you?
能把我给你的东西拼起来吗?
Can you put something together with what I gave you?
好了
Done.
-丹尼出来了吗?  -他就在那边角落里
-Is Danny about? -He's around the corner.
太棒了  能和真正的坏蛋共事真好
Terrific. It'll be nice working with proper villains again.
大家趴下! 全趴下!
Everybody down! Get down!
他们没料到还有这手吧
They weren't expecting that shit!
-干的漂亮 -多谢夸奖
-Nice work. -Thanks.
加里福尼亚州圣地亚哥
-哪位是了不起的袁?  -就是那个中国小家伙
-Which one's the Amazing Yen? -The little Chinese guy.
-候选的还有谁?  -就是他了
-Who else is on the list? -He is the list.
好象也不怎么...
It doesn't seem that diff--
-我们找到了滑溜溜的家伙 -我们找到了滑溜溜的家伙
-We got a grease man. -We got a grease man.
我们还需要索尔
We need Saul.
-一年前他就收手了 -他信教了?
-He got out of the game a year ago. -He get religion?
是因为溃疡
Ulcers.
-你可以去和他谈谈 -好  我去和他谈
-You could ask him. -Hey, I could ask him.
佛罗里达州圣彼得堡
我在赛马场就看见你了
I saw you at the paddock...
...是在第二场比赛还没开始前 在男子更衣室外
...before the second race, outside the men's room when I placed my bet.
今天早晨你没起床我就知道你要来
I saw you before you even got up this morning.
-最近怎么样  索尔?  -好的不能再好了
-How you been, Saul? -Never better.
桔子的味道怎么样?
What's with the orange?
医生说我要多摄入维生素
-My doctor says I need vitamins.
那为什么不直接吃维生素?
-Why don't you take vitamins?
你是来给我做体检的吗?
You come here to give me a physical?
去看台  来吧
Box seats. Come on.
你想要说服我吗?  还是我该拒绝  并把这事忘掉?
You gonna tell me? Or should I say no and get it over with?
你是这行最棒的  都上了名人堂 你有什么要求?
You're the best. You're in Cooperstown. What do you want?
没什么要求   我已经有了大房子
Nothing. I got a duplex now.
房子里全铺上了地毯   还养了金鱼
I got wall-to-wall and a goldfish.
我看上了快餐店的漂亮收银小姐
I'm seeing a lady who works the counter at Macy's.
我已经变了
I've changed.
我们这种人是不会变的 不是保持锋利那就是生锈
Guys like us don't change. We stay sharp or get sloppy.
别和我争了
Quit conning me.
你就打算永远受别人的规则左右?
That your hound way in the rear?
我最近一直在休息   这谁都知道
He breaks late. Everyone knows this.
你至少该把我当成是成年人
You going to treat me like a grownup at least?
告诉我是什么计划?
Tell me what the scam is?
他拥有最重量级拳王的金腰带
Exhibit C: His belt asking of the heavy weight crown.
利诺克斯路易斯证明了他就是冠军
Lennox Lewis has proved he 's the champion.
算上索尔就十个人了
Saul makes 10.
十个人该能办成这事  你觉得呢?
Ten should do it, don't you think?
你觉得我们还需要个人吗?
You think we need one more?
你觉得我们还需要个人
You think we need one more.
好  我们就再去找个人
Alright, we'll get one more.
伊利诺斯州芝加哥
干的漂亮!  在艾米特酒吧等你 -丹尼欧森
你好  莱纳斯  这是谁的?
Hello, Linus. Whose is this?
-你是谁?  -我是波比考德维尔的朋友
-Who are you? -A friend of Bobby Caldwell's.
你是否愿意加入? 做决定吧
You're either in or out. Right now.
-是什么?  -一张机票  一桩生意
-What is it? -It's a plane ticket. A job offer.
-为什么信任我 -波比对你的技术很有信心
-You're pretty trusting. -Bobby has faith in you.
父亲常那么说
Fathers are like that.
他没和你说吗?  他不想我走他的老路
He didn't tell you? He doesn't want me trading on his name.
做成了这事  你就超越了他
Do this job, he'll betrading on yours.
要是不成  你还能 继续做你的老行当
Don't, and you can go back to feeling up stockbrokers.
给我买单
Can you get the check, please?
那将是你从未有过的好假期
That's the best lift you've made yet.
拉斯维加斯?
Las Vegas?
美国的休养胜地
America's playground.
你们这就算是集齐了"鼠党"?
Did you guys get a group rate or something?
索尔  你不常离开犹他州吧?
Saul, do you get out to Utah much?
我不常出远门
Not as often as I'd like.
想想吧  你可以去爱尔兰共和军 在哪儿你会混的很好的
Check it out. I think you'd dig Provo. You could do well there.
我会考虑的
I'll look into it.
欢迎来到拉斯维加斯 都吃过了吗? 很好
Welcome to Las Vegas. Has everybody eaten? Good.
都还镇定吗?
Everybody sober?
都听好了  在行动开始前   谁都不算真正加入
Close enough. Before we start, nobody's on the line yet.
我的计划包含 有高利润和高风险
What I'm about to propose is highly lucrative and highly dangerous.
要是觉得不对胃口
If that's not your brand of vodka...
那就尽可能玩的开心点 不用再多考虑什么
...eat as much as you like and havea safe journey. No hard feelings.
要是对胃口了  那就跟我来
Otherwise, come with me.
你就是波比考德维尔的孩子?
You're Bobby Caldwell's kid?
-从芝加哥来?  -是的
-From Chicago? -Yeah.
-喜欢那儿吗?  -是的
-You like it there? -Yeah.
那就好  进屋里去吧
That's wonderful. Get in the goddamn house.
拉斯维加斯的3000号街区
The 3000 block ofLas Vegas Boulevard...
...就和美丽湖  蜃楼  大米高梅 这三家赌场一样出名
...also known as the Bellagio, Mirage and MGM Grand.
那是拉斯维加斯三家最赚钱的赌场
They' re three of the most profitable casinos in Las Vegas.
这是美丽湖赌场的金库
This is the Bellagio vault, located...
...位于地面200英尺以下
...beneath 200 feet of solid earth.
三个赌场间都有重重守卫把守
It safeguards every dime that passes through each of the three casinos.
-而我们计划打劫它们 -是武装抢劫吗?
-We're gonna rob it. -Smash-and-grab job?
比那要更复杂些
Slightly more complicated than that.
是嘛
Well, yeah.
这位是弗兰克卡顿   美丽湖赌场新来的操牌者
This is courtesy of Frank Catton,a new dealer at the Bellagio.
首先是坏消息
Bad news first.
这地方的安全保卫措施 赛过国家原子能中心
This place houses a security system rivaling most nuclear silos.
首先  我们要踏进赌场的门槛 进去时不止要面带微笑
First, we have to get in the casino cages, which takes more than a smile.
其次是要通过这些门...
Next, through these doors...
...每扇门的密码都不相同 而且每12小时就会更改
...each one requiring a different code changed every 1 2 hours.
过了那里  是电梯  那儿还有着机关
Past those, the elevator. Here's where it gets tricky.
过不了指纹锁  电梯是不会动的
-It won't move without finger print ID.
这步骤我们做不了假
-Which we can't fake.
同时还要通过 美丽湖金库的声音验证
And vocal confirmation from the system within the Bellagio and the vault.
那也是我们无法模仿的
Which we won't get.
电梯还装有传感装置
The elevator shaft is rigged with sensors.
如果查出了异状
If we override the lift,
出口会被锁死 我们就会被困在里面
the exit would lock and we'd be trapped.
下了电梯   有个小麻烦要料理
Once we get down the shaft, it's a piece of cake.
那儿有两个以上 带着乌兹冲锋枪的警卫
Just two more guards with Uzis...
...还有设计精巧的金库大门
...and the most elaborate vault door ever conceived.
还有问题吗?
Any questions?
我们为什么不从地下挖个洞   钻过去呢?
挖隧道是行不通的
Tunneling's out. There are...
地下设有传感器
...sensors monitoring the ground.
就算 只是土拨鼠的动静  他们也会察觉
If a ground hog nested, they'd know.
-还有吗?  -那有什么好消息没?
-Anyone else? -You mentioned good news?
是的  内华达赌博委员会要求...
Yeah. The Nevada Gaming Commission requires...
赌场必须保持足够多 的资金用作周转
...a casino to keep enough cash tocover every chip in play on the floor.
那就意味着平时那儿
That means on a weekday it must carry...
...就储存有至少 六到七千万的现金
...between $60 and $70 million in cash and coin.
而到了周末  甚至会有八千到九千万
On the weekend, between 80 and 90 million. On a fight night...
若是选在两周间拳赛的那天下手
...like in two weeks,the night we're robbing it...
我们就能毫不费力 的搞到一亿五千万
...$1 50 million, without breaking a sweat.
这儿共有11个人   这笔钱将会被平分
There are 11 of us, each with an equal share.
你们自己算吧
You do the math.
说的很对
Exactly.
我还有个问题
I have a question.
就算是我们通过了那些安全门
Say we get into the cage and through the security doors...
过了无法移动的电梯
...down the elevator we can't move...
避过那些警卫和枪 进入无法被打开的金库...
...past the guards with the guns,into the vault we can't open--
-还要不被监视器发现 -抱歉  我忘了提那点
-And not seen by cameras. -Sorry, I forgot to mention that.
对  就算是我们全躲过了
Yeah, well, say we do all that...
我们就能拿着那一亿五千万走出来
...we're just supposed to walk out of there with $1 50 million...
而毫不受阻拦?
...without getting stopped?
对
Yeah.
那就好
Oh. Okay.
首先的任务: 我要知道整个赌场的运作情况
First task: reconnaissance. I want to know what goes on...
从庄家的赌桌到现金运送的路径
...in all casinos, from the dealers' rotation...
我要知道所有守卫的所有动向
...to the path of cash carts. I want to know everything about every guard.
这个叫夏米的女孩
This girl Charmaine...
要了解他们来自哪里  别名 所有的生活细节
Find out where they're from, nicknames, how they take their coffee.
...也喜欢去疯马跳舞
...dances at Crazy Horse Too. It pays for her school.
-我想她喜欢我 -真棒
-I think she really likes me. -Cool.
要了解赌场的结构 建这些赌场就是让人进去
Know these casinos. They were built to keep people in.
要了解快速出口
Know the quick routes out.
他一般都是10: 44进去
-He went through at 10:44.
是10: 46  看看里面如何运作
-10:46. Get a watch that works.
-你可真讨厌  我说了是10: 44 -是10: 46
-You make me sick, dude. It's 10:44. -10:46.
第二个任务: 力量
Second task: power.
拳赛的那天晚上   我们要使这城市混乱
On fight night, we 'll throw the switch on Sin City.
巴舍  这就要看你的了
-Basher, it's your show.
你想要破坏这城市  让那儿漆黑一片
-You want broke, blind
或是造成混乱?
or bedlam?
-三者兼备如何?  -好  就那样
-How about all three? -Right, it's done.
第三个任务: 监控
Third task: surveillance.
安全人员眼观六路  耳听八方
Security has an eye and an ear on everything.
而我们也对他们来这套   利文斯顿  怎么样?
We want an eye and ear on them. Livingston?
入侵这系统对我来说并不难
It's not the least accessible system I've seen.
-那儿没有闭路线吗?  -没有
-There's no closed-circuit to tap into? -No.
那肯定是非法勾当 他们雇佣了内部技术人员?
Then it's definitely a black bag job. They employ an in-house technician?
有两人  其中一人很寂寞
Two. And one of them is lonely.
谢谢  夏米 一小时后还你
Thanks, Charmaine. I'll return it in an hour.
代我向你妈妈问好
-Say hi to your mom for me.
这可是你说的  她很快就会重回舞台
-Say it yourself. She's on-stage soon.
小心点  小鬼!
Watch it, bud!
-你叫我什么?  -我叫你伙计  朋友
-You call me bud, pal? -You call me pal, friend?
-你叫我朋友  蠢货?  -别叫我蠢货
-You call me friend, jackass? -Don't call me jackass.
433号注意   西北052出口摄像头监控受阻
433, we have a visual impair menton the northwest 052 exit-door camera.
收到  我看见了
Copy that. I see them.
闲人勿入
-那是个词吗? 不是你编的?  -"拍马屁"就是个
-Is that a word? You made that up? -" Obsequious" is a word.
-先生  请拿走你的气球 -是你挡了我的路!
-Sir, please move your balloons. -You got in my way!
-我只不过要去送气球!  -先生们!
-I was trying to deliver balloons! -Gentlemen!
-他是个送气球的小子!  -你的口水溅到我脸上了
-He's a balloon boy! Balloon boy! -You're spitting in my face.
我们开始运作了
And we're up and running.
走廊为何总是那种颜色?
-Why are hallways always that color?
有人说灰褐色让人精神放松
-They say taupe is very soothing.
-你好 -你好  谢谢
-Hi. -Fine, thanks.
-请把气球拿开 -拿开?
-Move the balloons. -Move them?
一位重要的客人在等着呢 我没时间...
An important client is waiting forthese. I don't have time...
对付你们这些马戏团的动物
...for you circus animals.
嘿  等等!
Hey! Hold up a minute!
对不起!
Excuse me!
Hey! Excuse me!
-你掉了这家伙 -哦  谢谢
-Hey, you dropped this. -Oh, thank you.
-这玩意的接收怎么样?  -非常好
-How's the reception on those things? -Excellent.
-小心些 -谢谢
-Take care. -Thanks.
-没事了... -对
-Well.... -Yeah.
第四个任务: 建筑
Fourth task: construction.
我们需要一个 美丽湖金库的复制品
We need to build an exact replica of the Bellagio vault.
-练习用?  -差不多
-To practice? -Something like that.
第五个任务: 情报 我们需要密码  莱纳斯...
Fifth task: intelligence. We need those codes, Linus...
从那个拥有这三家赌场 的人身上去搞吧
...from the guy who has all three.
-谁  本尼迪克特?  -要了解他的一举一动
-Who, Benedict? -Learn to love his shadow.
-我只需要整天看那家伙就行了?  -先学走后学爬
-All I get to do is watch the guy? -Gotta walk before you crawl.
-反过来 -第六个任务: 运送
-Reverse that. -Sixth task: transport.
我很抱歉  但每辆一万八千
Well, I am sorry, but $18,500 a piece
已经是我能出到的最低价钱了
is the best offer that I can make.
我明白
Well, I understand.
-这些车子很漂亮 -对  那是一流的
-They are some great-looking vans. -Yes, sir, top of the line.
-非常感谢...你叫?  -德纳姆  比利德纳姆
-Okay. Thank you for your time, Mr.. .? -Denham. Billy Tim Denham.
-德纳姆喜欢牛仔裤 -对  就喜欢这样的牛仔裤
-Denham like a jean. -That's it. Just like the jean.
你的手真软  是用了润肤霜吗?
Man, you got some lovely hands here. Do you moisturize?
-你说什么?  -我曾试过很多护肤液
-I'm sorry? -I've tried lots of lotion.
我还搽过一年的香水
I even went fragrance-free for a year. Now my sister...
现在我姐姐使用芦荟油掺遮光剂
...she uses aloe vera with a little sunscreen in it.
一般来说   我们睡觉时都该戴手套
Ideally, we all should wear gloves to bed...
...但那总是被我的工作所干扰
...but I found there was interference with my social agenda, you know.
此外我还对樟脑过敏   所以传统药物治疗对我无效
Plus, I react to the camphor. So I'm not into the traditional remedies.
我这么说吧  要是你用现金支付
Let me tell you something. If you could pay cash...
...我可以给你打七折...
...l could drop thatdown to seven--
每辆一万六
Sixteen each.
-不是吧?  -是的  先生
-No? -Yes, sir.
-你愿意那么做吗?  -是的  先生
-You'd do that? -Yes, sir.
那就太好了 他们就让我来找你就行
That'd be lovely. They told me to see you.
-很高兴他们这么说 -他们就是这么告诉我的
-Well, I'm glad they did. -They told me.
我去办下手续  请你在这儿等我
Well, let me go get the paperwork. You just wait here at the table.
-请便 -谢谢
-You do that. -Thank you.
-上等的衣料 -那是进口的丝绸  索尔
-Very nice material. -It's imported silk, Saul.
很好
It's very nice.
先生们  请先出去会好吗?
Gentlemen, would you excuse us for a second? Thanks.
索尔  你肯定自己 已经做好准备了吗?
Saul, you sure you're ready to do this?
若是你再问我这问题  丹尼
If you ever ask me that question again, Daniel...
明早你会没命起床的
...you won't wake up the following morning.
他准备好了
He's ready.
我叫莱曼
My name is Lyman...
...泽加
...Zerga.
我叫莱曼泽加
My name is Lyman Zerga.
好  和我说说本尼迪克特的事
Okay, tell me about Benedict.
这家伙简直是台机器
That guy's a machine.
下午好
Good afternoon.
每天下午两点他会到美丽湖酒店
He arrives at the Bellagio every day at 2 p. m.
你好  汤米
How are you, Tommy?
他甚至记得所有侍应的名字
He remembers every valet's name.
对于身价七八亿的富翁来说   这已经是很不容易
Not bad for a guy worth 3/4 ofa billion.
他工作很拼命   每天七点准时到会议室...
He works hard, hits the lobby floor at 7 on the nose.
-晚上好  先生 -你好吗?
-Good evening, sir. -How are you?
-和赌场的经理谈话 -谈些什么?
-Talks with his casino manager. -About what?
所有生意的事
All business.
本尼迪克特乐于知道发生了什么 喜欢一切都在掌握中
Benedict likes to know what's going on. Be in control.
赌场里几乎没有什么事情 是他所不知道的
There 's rarely an incident he doesn't know about or handle personally.
他还会花上小会时间去招呼贵宾
Spends a few minutesglad-handing the high rollers.
他会说西班牙语  德语  意大利语 还有日语也不错
He speaks Spanish, German and ltalianand is getting good at Japanese.
七点三十他会出去   接一份黑色的文件夹
He 's out by 7:30 and is handed a black portfolio.
内容包括营业邀和新的安全密码 然后就朝餐厅走去
Contents: profits and new security codes. He heads to the restaurant.
就象我说的  真是台机器
Like I said, a machine.
文件里的密码能开所有的门吗?
That portfolio containscodes to all the cage doors?
他们更换新密码后两分钟   他就拿到了密码
And two minutes after they're changed, he's got them.
你们可真会挑下手的对象 他是个既聪明又残忍的家伙
You guys really can pick them. This guy's as smart as he is ruthless.
上个被他抓到使诈的家伙   不但被他搞至判十年
Last guy he caught cheating, he not only sent up for 10 years...
而且他还占了那家伙的房产
...he seized his house and bankrupted his--
和合法的特约店
In-law's dealership.
他会要了你的命  毁了你的生活 大家都知道这点
He takes out your knees and ruins your life and anybody you know.
你怕了?
You scared?
难道你想自杀吗?
You suicidal?
只有早上想
Only in the morning.
-现在他会干什么?  -现在该那女孩出来
-Now what? -Now comes the girl.
如果时间急的话   她会和他一起下来
She comes down after him if they' re in a snit.
-她是哪儿来的?  -博物馆  她是馆长
-Where does she come from? -The museum, there. She's the curator.
她来了
Here she is.
这是我一天中最美好的时光
This is the best part of my day.
不知道是否能利用到她   我甚至还没问到她的名字
I'm not sure we can use her yet. I haven't even caught her name.
泰丝
Tess.
什么?
Huh?
她叫泰丝
Her name is Tess.
-我们得谈谈 -可以
-We have to talk. Now. -Okay.
告诉我不是因为她才干这事的 否则我就退出
Tell me this is not about her or I walk off the job.
谁?
Who?
泰丝   本尼迪克特   告诉我你不是报复他...
Tess. Benedict. Tell me this isn't about...
-搞上你妻子 -是前妻
-...the guy who's screwing your wife. -Ex-wife.
-告诉我 -不是那样的
-Tell me. -It's not about that.
完全跟那没关系 记得我们开始商量计划时说的吗?
It's not entirely about that. Remember when we got in this business?
我们说过  已经一无所有 的人就不会输
We said we'd play like we had nothing to lose.
我是真的一无所有了
Well, I lost something.
我失去了某人   所以我来了这里
I lost someone. That's why I'm here.
问题是  现在我们要偷两样东西
The problem is, now we're stealing two things.
若是不能两者兼得   你会选哪个?
And if you can't have both, which do you choose?
要记得   泰丝不能分裂这十一人
Remember, Tess does not split 11 ways.
若一切进展顺利   事情就不是由我说了算的
If everything goes to plan, I won't be the one that has to make that choice.
-她现在怎样?  -她看来好极了
-How'd she look? -She looked good.
谢谢
Thanks.
你喜欢吗?
You like it?
我只喜欢你喜欢的东西
I like that you like it.
-今晚我来找你好吗?  -好的
-I'll see you tonight? -Okay.
在我的酒店里   总会被人看到
In my hotel, there's always somebody watching.
今晚见
I'll see you tonight.
胃不好吗? 泽加先生
Weak stomach, Mr.Zerga?
我从不迷信脆弱  那代价太高
I don't believe in weakness. It costs too much.
我也不迷信问题本身
I don't believe in questions either.
是吗? 那么我给你提个醒吧
Oh, really? Well then,let me give you a tip.
别赢特瑞本尼迪克特那么多钱
Don't get into Terry Benedict for too much money.
他可不是傻瓜
He doesn't fool around.
-你好吗  埃迪?  -很好  先生
-How are you, Eddie? -Fine, sir.
有什么动向吗?
Anything for me?
莱曼泽加先生  那边第三位 想要和你私下谈谈
Mr.Lyman Zerga. Third position. Wants to talk to you privately.
他是谁?
Who is he?
欧洲来的生意人
Businessman of some kind,from Europe.
不清楚是干什么的
Very vague.
不过我打听过了 好象是做军火走私的
I asked around. Word is, he deals primarily in arms.
-还是个大军火商 -泽加
-One of the biggest. -Zerga.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
-从未听说过 -所以我并没有怀疑
-Never heard of him. -That's why I don't doubt it.
-他住在这儿吗?  -就住在塔楼套间
-He's staying here? -He's in the Mirador suite.
-赌的怎么样?  -手气还不错
-How's he doing? -Up, almost 200.
很好
Good for him.
你晚来了三十秒 我正要派人...
You're 30 seconds late. I was about to send out a search....
好啊  泰丝
Hello, Tess.
你来这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
我出来了
I'm out.
-出来了?  -从监狱里出来的
-Out? -Of prison.
还记得吗?  我去做烟草买卖  结果就没回来
Remember? I went for cigarettes and didn't come back.
我从不抽烟  你别坐
I don't smoke. Don't sit.
我想向社会偿付我的罪债
-Supposedly I paid my debt to society.
那可好笑了  我从未收到过帐单
-Funny, I never got a check.
你没有戴戒指了
You're not wearing your ring.
我已经卖了  我已经没有丈夫
I sold it. I don't have a husband
你难道没收到离婚通知吗?
or didn't you get the papers?
-我在里面最后一天收到的 -我告诉你我写过信
-My last day inside. -I told you I'd write.
丹尼  在他来之前你最好快走...
-Danny, go now before--
谁? 本尼迪克特?
-What? Benedict?
你好  来威士忌
How you doing? Whiskey and whiskey.
你在博物馆干的不错 维米尔的作品很优秀
You're doing a great job at the museum. The Vermeer is quite good.
充满了活力  不过后期的作品就差了
-Vibrant. But his work fell off later.
那让你想起谁了?
-Remind you of anyone?
我常把蒙纳和曼纳搞混 是谁娶了他的情妇?
I always confuse Monet and Manet. Which one married his mistress?
-是蒙纳 -是蒙纳娶了谢菲莉斯
-Monet. -And Manet had syphilis.
后来他们偶尔还会画画
They also painted occasionally.
行了  长话短说
All right, I'll make this quick.
我来这儿是为了找你
I came here for you.
我想要从头开始生活 我需要你
I want to get on with my life. I want you with me.
你既是贼又是骗子
You're a thief and a liar.
我在做贼的事情上是骗了你 可现在不会了
I lied about being a thief. I don't do that now.
-不再偷了?  -是不再对你撒谎
-Steal? -Lie.
现在和我一起的人
I'm with someone who doesn't have to make...
-可没你这样的坏名声 -他和我一样清白
-...that kind of distinction. -He's clear on both.
-知道你的问题所在吗?  -我只有一个问题
-You have a problem. -Only one?
你找到了太多同类 而我现在和特瑞在一起
You've met too many people like you. I'm with Terry now.
他令你开心吗?
Does he make you laugh?
他不会令我哭泣
He doesn't make me cry.
-拳赛是在周末晚上?  -对  想要票吗?
-The fight is Saturday night? -Yes, would you like tickets?
不  我对赤手空拳的打不感兴趣
No. Hand-to-hand combat does not interest me.
那晚上我有批货要到
I have a package arrivinghere that evening.
黑色公文箱  标准尺寸
A black briefcase, standard size...
里面的东西对我来说很重要
...the contents of which is very valuable to me.
我会帮你妥善保管在安全房中
I'll put it in the house safe.
安全房是用放白兰地 和祖母的珍珠的
The house safe is for brandy and grandmother's pearls.
-我需要更安全的地方 -泽加先生  我可以向你担保...
-I need something more secure. -Mr.Zerga, I can assure you our--
我也可以向你保证
I can assure you,
本尼迪克特先生 若是你在这事上帮到了我
Mr.Benedict,that your generosity in this matter...
那么将来必有回报
...will not go overlooked.
除了安全你还能给我什么?
Now, what can you offer me besides the safe?
你们专偷保了险的人 他们转眼又会重建江山
People you steal from have insurance. They get made whole again.
我离开纽约是为了避开那儿的事 谁能还我五年的光阴?
I left New York to escape what happened. Can I get five years back?
-你不应该抛弃... -你什么也不知道
-What you can do is not throw---You don't know anything.
你不再爱我了   你有了新欢  很好
You don't love me,you're with someone else, fine.
我能适应这局面 可是由他来取代我就是不行
I have to live with that. But not him.
就是前夫的口气
Just like an ex-husband.
-我没在开玩笑 -我也没有笑
-I'm not joking. -I'm not laughing.
在谈到我的感情生活的一块
There's a conflict of interest when you...
-我们有了利益冲突 -对  但那不意味着我说错了
-...give me advice about my love life. -But that doesn't mean I'm wrong.
记得我们初次相遇时 我对你说什么来着?
Do you remember what I said when we first met?
-"我该知道我在干什么" -是吗? 现在呢?
-That I better know what I'm doing. -Do you? Now?
若是不明白  那你最好现在就走
You should go if you don't.
我知道我在干什么
I know what I'm doing.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
来的正是时候
Just catching up.
-来认识下我的前夫吧 -丹尼欧森
-Meet my ex-husband. -Danny Ocean.
-欧森先生 -我坐了你的位置
-Mr.Ocean. -I'm in your seat.
请原谅我来迟了 有位客户有事相求
Forgive my lateness. A guest required my attention.
没关系  丹尼只是路过   刚好看见了我
That's fine. Danny was walking through and spotted me.
-是吗?  -想象下这可能性吧
-Is that so? -Imagine the odds.
"人生何处不相逢"
" Of all the gin jointsin all the world. "
刚从监狱里出来?
You recently were released from prison?
没错
That's right.
-出来的感觉如何?  -一样
-How does it feel to be out? -About the same.
-丹尼打算... -我只是想来向泰丝问个好
-Danny was just about to-I just stopped by to say hi to Tess.
坐会  喝杯酒吧
Stay, have a drink.
-我还有事 -他还有事
-I can't. -He can't.
好吧  那么...
Well, then....
我想我们很快就见不到欧森先生了
I imagine we won't see Mr.Ocean anytime soon.
谁知道呢
You never know.
我知道我酒店发生的所有事
I know everything happening in my hotels.
那我该把这些毛巾放回去
So I should put those towels back.
不  你留着吧
No, the towels you can keep.
-见到你真好  泰丝 -保重  丹尼
-Good to see you, Tess. -Take care, Danny.
-特瑞 -丹尼
-Terry. -Danny.
真讨厌...
Stinking....
明天就是行动的大日子
Tomorrow the day is yours.
五点三十起床  然后是化装
Call is at 5:30, makeup and costume.
索尔的行李将在七点零五分到 莱纳斯去取密码
Saul's package arrives at 7:05. Linus grabs our codes.
到了七点半  一切该准备就绪
All goes well, we're a go. At 7:30,
袁会被锁在里面  而我们就分头行动
Yen is locked in and we're committed.
我们只有三十分钟时间   不然他就会在里面窒息而死
From this point, we have 30 minutes to blow the power or he suffocates.
断电后立即前往金库
Once the electricity goes,access to the vault...
停电时间为两分钟   我们就趁机进入
...and its elevator shut down for two minutes. That's when we go.
你位于金库的的正中   距离所有的东西都有十英尺远
You're in the middle of the room, 10 feet from everything.
你要直接到门那儿   而不能碰到地板
You have to get to the door without touching the floor.
你怎么样?
What do you do?
-十秒对他来说少了点 -那就二十秒
-Ten says he shorts it. -Twenty.
从窗户还是走道?
Window or aisle, boys?
是的  我们有大麻烦了
Yeah, we're in deep shit.
事情无法按原计划进行
That poxy demo crew didn't back the main line.
他们把主电机给破坏了   全弄坏了!
They naused up the mainframe. Naused it up!
-他这是在说什么?  -等会我会解释的
-You understand him? -I'll explain later.
他们就愚蠢的把那里全毁了
They' re so pony they blew the backup grids one by one.
巴舍  出了什么事?
Basher, what happened?
由于意外  现在他们 把我要干的事给做了
They did what I would have done but by accident.
现在他们知道自己是多么无用了 他们在修复那里
Now they know their weakness,they're fixing it.
所以这不是在里诺办这事 我们有麻烦了
So unless we intend to do this jobin Reno, we're in Barney.
麻烦  大麻烦
Barney Rubble. Trouble!
-我们可以... -明天?
-We could always-By tomorrow?
等等  我们可以使用收缩器
Hang on a minute, hang on. We could use a pinch.
什么是收缩器?
What's a pinch?
那装置能造成宽带电缆的短路
A device which creates a cardiacarrest for broadband circuitry.
换句话说   收缩器是没有炸药的炸弹
Better yet, a pinch is abomb without the bomb.
当核弹被引爆时   其电磁辐射脉冲
When a nuclear weapon detonates, its electromagnetic pulse...
...能使爆炸半径内 的一切动力源失去作用
...shuts down any power source within its blast radius.
通常这不会被注意 因为核爆本身就摧毁了所有的事物
It usually doesn't matter because a nuclear weapon destroys everything.
收缩器可以制作出相同的电磁辐射
A pinch creates a similar electromagnetic pulse...
而不会造成任何破坏和伤亡
...without mass destruction and death.
不会有象在日本广岛那样的惨剧
Instead of Hiroshima you get...
能持续多久?
-...the 17th century. -How long?
三十秒
30 seconds.
收缩器能中止整个城市的电源吗?
Could a pinch knock outthe power of an entire city?
-就象  举例来说... -能中断拉斯维加斯的电源吗?
-Like, for instance-Las Vegas?
对  我想应该能行
Yeah, I think it might.
只要有足够大收缩器就行
There's only one pinch big enough to do it.
哪儿有?
Where?
加州尖端科技学院 东大门
走吧  袁  巴舍  快点
Let's go. Yen, Basher, come on.
你要去哪儿?
Where you going?
-我跟你们一起去 -不
-I'm coming with you. -No.
不  不! 别把我留下 和这些家伙在一起!
Oh, no, no, no! Don't leave me with these guys!
开始吧
Start.
-我有办法了 -你在想办法?
-I got one. -You thinking of one?
-不  我已经想好了 -你不过是在想而已
-No, I've thought of one. -You're thinking of one.
不  已经想好了  已经成熟了
No, I'm done. I have it.
-你是男人吗?  -对  19了
-You a man? -Yes. 1 9.
-你活着吗?  -对  活了18年了
-You alive? -Yes. 18.
-伊瓦艾卡尼夫 -混蛋!
-Evel Knievel. -Shit!
-别碰我 -我没碰你
-Don't touch me. -I'm not.
-你的手碰到我脸了 -没有
-Your hand's in my face. -It's not.
-我碰了你吗?  -你的手碰到了我的脸
-Am I touching you? -Your hand's in my face.
-拿开 -我没有碰你
-Move. -I didn't touch you.
-你刚刚就在碰我 -是你拿我的手碰你的
-You just touched me. -You made me touch you.
别超到这边来  别超过来
This is your side. This is your side.
滚开  滚开
Get off. Get off.
我需要二十个汽车电池...
I'm gonna need a score of car batteries--
莱纳斯去哪了? 莱纳斯呢?
Where's Linus? Where's Linus?
-他在那儿 -看到那个白痴了吗?
-There he is. -Oh, would you look at this doughnut?
他不听我们的   他已经死定了
该叫人去帮他吗?
Should someone help him?
真是好主意  阿尔伯特 大家都去送死吧
That's a great idea, Albert. Let's all get nicked.
倒回去
Back it up.
拉他进来
Let him in.
你这个蠢货!
You stupid bastard!
-我说别动你就该别动 -知道了
-I say stay, you stay. -Got it.
安静会  有人受伤了!
Lose focus for one second, somebody gets hurt!
我知道了
I got it.
他们在哪儿?
Where are they?
我也想知道   他们到底是去哪儿了?
That's what I want to know. Where the hell are they?
-他们会回来的 -"他们会回来的"  低能儿!
-They will be here. -"They will be here. " Schmuck!
玩的开心吗?
You boys have a nice trip?
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
你已经被盯上了
You've been red-flagged.
你一进赌场   他们就开始监视你
The moment you enter the casino,they'll be watching.
就象鹰一样  带着摄像头的鹰
Like hawks. Hawks with video cameras.
问题就在这儿
That's a problem.
-索尔  把电视关掉 -等我准备好...
-Saul, turn that off. -When I'm ready--
-索尔!  -关了! 关了!
-Saul! -It's off! It's off!
知道这是怎么回事吗?
Any idea how this happened?
-不知道 -算了吧
-No. -Oh, come on.
他在追本尼迪克特的女人 两天前的晚上他们还吵过一架
He's been chasing Benedict's girl. They had an argument two nights ago.
-我跟踪你了 -谁让你这么干的?
-I tailed you. -Who told you to?
是我  我就怕你会找泰丝
I did. I worried you couldn't leave Tess alone.
-泰丝?  -我妻子
-Tess? -My wife.
-是前妻 -泰丝在这儿?
-Ex-wife. -Tess is here?
抱歉  我不知道这会伤到你
I'm sorry. I didn't know if it would sting you, but it did.
-你被出局了  丹尼 -他出局?
-You're out, Danny. -He's out?
不然就取消计划 他会给我们招来麻烦
Or we call it off. His involvement puts us at risk.
-轮不到你来发号施令 -你是自作自受
-It's not your call. -You put her before us and made it mine.
这是我的生意
This is my job.
不再是了
Not anymore.
他不能被踢出局 谁来负责开金库的门?
He can't just be out. Who's gonna trigger the vault?
小鬼  你行吗?
Kid, you up for it?
可以
I can do it.
行了  找到其他人 告诉他们计划有变
Done. Locate the others. Tell them the change in plan.
行动在七点进行
Curtain goes up at 7.
泰丝现在和本尼迪克特在一起?  她的个子可比他要高呢
Tess is with Benedict now? She's too tall for him.
对  不行
Yes. No.
绝对不行
Very much no.
告诉列温先生   他最好在家里看比赛
Then inform Mr.Levin he'll be better off watching the fight at home on TV.
当然  他能收到HBO 就这样
Surely, he must have HBO. That's it.
嗨
Hi.
在想什么呢?
What were you thinking about?
想你
You.
打算把手放在哪儿?
Where you gonna put your hands?
不怎么好
No good.
别去碰领带  看着我
Don't touch your tie. Look at me.
只需回答我的问题 你在看什么?
You need to answer my question. Where do you look?
不能向下看  他们会知道你在撒谎
No. Look down, they know you're lying.
向上看  做出一无所知的样子
Up, and you don't know the truth.
别说些辞不达意的废话
Don't use seven words if four will do.
说话要明确  但别太深刻 要幽默  但别让对方发笑
Be specific, but not memorable. Be funny, but don't make him laugh.
那样对方会喜欢 而当你转身就会把你忘掉
He's got to like you,then forget you once you leave.
还有  看在上帝份上 无论你要做什么  千万不要...
And, for God's sake, whatever you do, don't--
拉斯! 过来看看这个好吗?
Russ! Can you take a look at this?
好
Sure.
索尔?
Saul?
该出发了
It's time.
行了
Okay.
出发吧
Let's do it.
在这个拉斯维加斯的美丽夜晚
On a perfectly clear night in Las Vegas...
大群的名人和体育迷们
...with the expected crowd of celebrities and sports fans...
聚集在大米高梅酒店 两位世界上最棒的拳击选手
...piling into the MGM Grand, the two best heavyweights in the world...
正准备继续八个月前的较量 再次一较高下
...prepare to meet after aneight-month dance toward each other.
泽加先生?
Mr.Zerga?
本尼迪克特先生
Mr.Benedict.
-我很忙  东西准时到吗?  -换成我就绝对不会怀疑
-I'm very busy. Are we on schedule? -I have no reason to suspect otherwise.
我的人即刻就会到
My courier should be here momentarily.
十八  二十一点!
Eighteen. Blackjack!
去找威尔什先生 告诉他欧森先生正去西通道
Find Mr.Walsh. Tell him Mr.Ocean is in the west slots.
在赌场里我不能安排保镖
I can't have private security personnel in the casino cages.
是不能
Of course not.
索尔! 索尔布鲁  是你吗?
Saul! Saul Bloom, is that you?
索尔! 索尔  是我呀!  是布奇巴卡南!
Saul! Saul, it's me! Bucky Buchanan!
记得吗?  我们在萨拉托加见过!
Remember? From Saratoga!
把他给我轰走
Mikael. Vladimir.
嘿  索尔! 索尔!
Hey! Hey, Saul! Saul!
本尼迪克特先生  请快点
Mr.Benedict, please.
我不喜欢钢铁碰着皮肤的感觉
I have never enjoyed the touch of steel to my skin.
把它们拿开
Lift them up, please.
我承认你的公文箱 没有危险性  或是违法
I acknowledge your briefcase contains nothing dangerous or illicit.
我同意将这公文箱 放入我的金库保管
I agree to take said briefcase and store it in my vault...
保管期为24小时
...for a period of 24 hours.
-可我不能允许你进金库 -为什么不行?
-I cannot allow you into the vault. -Why not?
出于安全上的考虑   可更多的是我不信任你
Insurance, for one. Security. But,most of all, I just don't trust you.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我叫了两个人盯住欧森 他现在在五球吧
I put two plain clothes on Ocean. He's in the keno bar now.
泽加先生  这是赌场经理   威尔什先生
Mr.Zerga, this is my casino manager, Mr.Walsh.
他会将你的公文箱放入金库
He will have your briefcase stored in our vault while you watch.
这是我们的条件  你同意与否?
Those are my terms. Yes or no?
你根本没给我选择的余地
You leave me no choice.
别在收缩器前面那么干
Dude, don't do that in front of the pinch.
深呼吸  你会办成的
Deep breaths. You 'll do fine.
-谢谢 -别流汗  自然点
-Thank you. -No sweat. You 're a natural.
但是别太做作了
But don 't screw up.
-谁叫的面食?  -放这儿
-Who gets the penne? -Right here.
准备好了吗?
You ready?
这儿是保安中心   负责监视赌场和金库
This is our security center,where we oversee the casino and vault.
你可以在这儿看到 公文箱的动向
You'll monitor your briefcase from here.
您请便吧
Don't let me keep you.
-泽加先生 -本尼迪克特先生
-Mr.Zerga. -Mr.Benedict.
莱纳斯  准备
Linus, you're up.
跟着他
Got him.
本尼迪克特先生
Mr.Benedict.
我是谢尔顿威利斯 内华达州赌博委员会的
Sheldon Willis, Nevada Gaming Commission.
能给我两分钟谈谈吗?
I need two minutes of your time.
-愿意为赌博委员会效劳 -谢谢
-Anything for the NGC. -Thanks.
能带我去五号厅吗?
Will you accompany me to pit five, please?
-打算什么时候推箱子进去?  -等你的信号
-You make the deposit when? -At your signal.
我们看起来象什么   向象不象对啄木鸟?
What do we look like,a couple of peckerwood jackasses?
感觉如何? 没事吧?
How does that feel? You all right?
想拿本什么看的吗?  要不要给你本杂志?
Want something to read? A magazine?
好了  把这记下来
All right. Counting down.
现在开始有三十分钟休息时间
Thirty minutes of breathing time starts now.
我们今天开始注意他的
This just came to our attention today.
显然  他有份记录要比我...
Apparently, he's got a record longer than my....
反正就是很久
It's long.
你说他是  那就是了
If he is who you say he is.
你在委员会干多久了?
You been at the commission long?
-大约18个月吧 -认识哈利林德里吗? 和他共事过吗?
-About 18 months. -You know Hal Lindley? Worked with him?
去年他死后就没有了
Not since he died last year.
拉蒙艾斯克拉特?
Ramon Escalante?
这位是谢尔顿威利斯 内华达州赌博委员会的
Sheldon Willis, Nevada Gaming Commission.
这是怎么会事?
What's going on here?
-根据我们了解... -我们去里面说
-It's come to our attention-We should speak off the floor.
查理
Charlie.
谢谢
Thank you.
-不  我要你离开这里 -给我点时间
-No. I want you out of here. -Give me one moment.
-我给过你时间了  现在我要你走 -泰丝  过来
-I've had it. I want you gone. -Tess, come here.
你来这儿干什么
You're up to something.
别对我说是来找我的 你又在动谁的主意了  不是吗?
Don't say you're here for me. You're pulling a job, aren't you?
好  不管你想干什么   你都不会把我赢回去的
Well, no matter what it is,you won't win me back.
泰丝  我是来说再见的
Tess, I just came to say goodbye.
再见
Goodbye.
没事的
You be good.
-欧森先生 -本尼迪克特先生想要见你
-Mr.Ocean. -Mr.Benedict wishes to see you.
我想也会是他找我
I thought he might.
下午好  艾斯克拉特先生
Good afternoon, Mr.Escalante.
或者我该称呼你为卡顿先生?
Or should I call you Mr.Catton?
你叫弗兰克卡顿   曾在特非卡那的沙漠旅馆工作
You're Frank Catton, of the Tropicana, the Desert lnn...
还曾被关入纽约州监狱  是吗?
...and the New York State Penitentiary system. Are you not?
保持沉默就是你对此毫无异义了?
I take it from your silence you won't refute that.
本尼迪克特先生
Mr.Benedict, you're employing an ex-convict.
你雇佣了一名前科犯  如你所知...
As you know--
该死的白人穷小子
Goddamn cracker.
-你说什么?  -你听的很清楚
-Excuse me? -You heard me.
黑人不能有正当职业吗?
Black man can't earn a decent wage?
-你想把我扔到大街上 -我只是在行公务
-You wanna throw me on the street. -I'm doing my job.
想要我到桌上来跳只舞吗?
Want me to get on the table and dance?
要我给你擦鞋吗?  要我对你微笑吗?
Shine your shoes? Smile at you?
你当然不想让我去操牌
You sure won't let me deal the cards.
连游戏的名字你也想黑白颠倒
You might as well call it whitejack!
我不知道该说什么 莱斯什么也没错
I don't know what to say to that. Race has nothing to do with it.
-是啊 -你说的过分了点
-Yeah, right. -What a horrible thing to say!
你们  所有的人
You, of all people,
都知道 赌博委员会也支持雇佣有色人种...
know the NGC has always supported hiring colored--
-不! 我不是这意思!  -好  算了  坐下
-No! I didn't mean it! -Okay. Come on, sit down.
-坐下 -你该和他好好谈谈
-Sit down. -You better talk to him.
-他做的很好 -坐下
-He's got it. -Sit down.
维吉尔  土克 把包裹送进去
Virgil. Turk. Deliver the package.
-你的卡呢?  -我丢了
-Where's your card? -I lost it.
-开什么玩笑?  -我真是太蠢了
-You serious? -I'm so stupid.
-你真是太蠢了! 知道吗?  -嗨!
-You are so stupid! You know that? -Hey!
在谁烦恼的时候直呼其名字好吗?
You think it helps to call someone names who's upset?
-都冷静些 -抱歉  抱歉
-Hey! IKeep it down. -Sorry. Sorry.
-这些钱是从哪儿送来的?  -是从贵宾房来的
-Where did this come from? -High roller's room.
-是本尼迪克特先生的东西 -乔  把这送进去
-It's Mr.Benedict's stuff. -Joe, take this inside.
-送去结算间?  -不  要直接进金库
-Count room? -No, to the vault.
本尼迪克特的钱该直接进金库
Benedict's money goes in the vault.
下次要记得带卡   再这样就不行方便了
Next time, remember the card, and we won't run into this again.
-蠢货 -天!
-Stupid. -Jeez!
请等等
Yo! Hold that, please.
-那儿就是你的公文箱  泽加先生 -很好
-There's your briefcase now, Mr.Zerga. -Wonderful.
该我上场了
That's my cue.
叫巴舍出发
Give Basher the go.
巴舍  你的位置?
Bash, what's your status?
-巴舍!  -轻点  没必要大喊大叫的
-Bash! -Easy. No need to shout, guv' ner.
-你的位置?  -就快就位了
-What's your status? -I'm nearly there.
来  来
Come on, come on.
威尔什先生  别让这家伙露面
Mr.Walsh, show this man off the premises.
不许再来我的赌场
Don't ever set footin my casino again.
先生?
Sir?
-白人穷小子!  -天!
-Cracker! -Oh, dear God!
我忘了拿呼机 我把那拉下了  抱歉
Oh! I forgot my pager. I left it. Sorry.
-知道回来的路吗?  -知道
-Know the way back? -I do.
那就好
Good.
好好欣赏比赛
Okay. Enjoy the fight.
抱歉!
Sorry!
你们说本尼迪克特先生 还要多久才来?
How much longer you figure Mr.Benedict's gonna be?
这房间没监视器吧?
No cameras in this room, huh?
看来是的
Yeah.
不让任何人看到 这儿会发生什么事
Don't want anybody seeing what goes on in here.
他不会来了  是吗?
He's not coming, is he?
我们出去  你们两个 在里面好好谈谈
We're gonna step outside. Leave you two to talk things over.
我已经三个礼拜没见我老婆了
I hadn't seen my wife in three weeks,
所以我决定打电话给她
so I decided to call her.
"我爱你  你爱我" "我想你  你想我"
"I love you, you love me. ""I miss you, you miss me. "
事情又变好了  可当我参加完舞会
That went well, but then I went to this party....
我到一点才回家   可她以为我会十一点就回去
I show up at 1 p. m. She expected me at 11 a. m...
于是她就发怒了 我说"你以为有什么? "
...so she was going crazy. I said, "What do you expect?
"你以为是什么?  这又不是唱诗班练习"
What do you think goes on? It's not choir practice. "
完了
Oh, shit.
那令你满意吗? 泽加先生
Does that satisfy you, Mr.Zerga?
我非常满意
I am very satisfied.
-你没事吧  先生?  -我很好  很好
-Are you all right, sir? -I'm fine. I'm fine.
好吧
All right.
老天!
Jesus!
布鲁瑟!
Bruiser!
-现在停还不算迟!  -对不起  丹尼  我没看出是你
-Not until later! -Sorry, Danny. I forgot.
没关系
It's all right.
-你妻子怎么样子?  -又怀孕了
-How's your wife? -Pregnant again.
很好  我们开始吧  来这儿
Well, it happens. Let's get started. Come here.
-你就快出来了  莱纳斯 -那家伙是谁?
-You're almost there, Linus. -Who's that guy?
-我在西走廊发现可疑人物 -泽加先生!
-I got a bogey in west corridor. -Mr.Zerga!
-叫医生来! 泽加先生!  -把这盖在他头上
-Call a doctor! Mr.Zerga! -Put this under his head.
现在切换影象
Going to video now.
急救中心吗
--to the Eye in the Sky ASAP.
这儿有位昏迷的人需要急救
We have a man down who's unconscious.
天啊!
Oh, Jesus!
-你真以为我会袖手旁观?  -你不相信我?
-Did you really think I'd sit this out? -You didn't trust me?
现在我相信了
I do now.
来吧
Come on.
有人叫医生吗?
Someone call for a doctor?
-你是怎么进来的?  -给个朋友两百万就行了
-How'd you get here? -Had to give a friend two million.
那拉斯提呢? 你们为什么吵?
But what about Rusty? The argument?
那也是计划一部分吗?
I mean, what was that about?
拜托  为什么不告诉我?  别把我排在局外
Come on. Why not just tell me? Why put me through all this?
这有什么意思? 走吧
Where's the fun in that? Let's get going.
来吧  伙计! 呼吸!
Come on, man! Breathe!
呼吸! 该死的! 呼吸!
Breathe, damn it! Breathe!
抱歉  他已经死了
I'm sorry. We've lost him.
-我叫你快点的 -别那样  真的别那样
-Dude, I told you to hurry. -Don't do that. Just don't.
我没让你快点吗?
I didn't tell you to hurry?
来  给我起来!
Come on, get up! Get up!
觉的怎么样?
Had enough yet?
-这些玩意撑得住我们吧?  -当然可以
-These things are gonna hold us, right? -They should.
利文斯顿  我们已经就位
Livingston, we're set.
-利文斯顿  我们已经就位 -巴舍  我们已经就位
-Livingston, we're set. -Basher, we're set.
等等  老大
Hang on a minute, chief.
我们得快点了  袁就快要窒息了
We don 't have one. Yen 's gonna suffocate.
你安静点  别烦我好吗?
Then you should leave off bothering me, okay?
好了  把那弄亮
All right, crack them.
走
Go.
该死!
Shit!
断
Cut it.
嗨!
Hey!
六厅  五号台操牌员受到袭击
Pit six, table five. Dealers compromised.
三号  五号  六号  十号台出现问题
Trade's breached at tables three,five, six and ten.
穿上衣服  穿上衣服
Get your coat. Get your coat.
真是都疯了! 怎么...?
Look, this is crazy! What...?
还不行
Not yet. Not yet.
上去
Go ahead.
-你觉得袁会搞定里面的事吗?  -我相信他会办好的
-You think Yen made it out okay? -I'm sure he'll be fine.
进行的怎么样?
How we doing?
我想应该是一切正常
Okay, I guess.
这门后有一亿六千万 和一个九十五磅的中国人
There's a 95-pound Chinese man with $160 million behind this door.
-把他弄出来吧 -对
-Let's get him out. -Yeah.
-我押十块赌他不会成功 -别乱说
-10 says he shorts it. -No bet.
再试试
Try him again.
很好
Okay.
进行到哪部分了?
Hey. Where we at, boys?
-破除监视和地板感应装置 -把他们弄瞎
-Pins and floor sensors, now. -Blinding.
行动吧
Here we go.
20秒倒数计时
Counting down from 20. Now.
20...
Twenty...
-停止炸门  听到了吗?  -10...
-Don't blow the door. Can you read me? -Ten...
...9  8...
...nine, eight...
-可能他的耳机出了问题 -不要炸门!
-Maybe the pinch blew out his ear wigs. -Do not blow the door!
...2  1
...two, one.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
有点问题...
Something....
放了电池吗?
Did you check the batteries?
稍微等一下就可以了
You know, lose focus in this game for one second--
我知道  有人受伤了 你真是没听过袁抱怨的声音
I know, somebody gets hurt. You don't hear Yen complaining.
袁?
Yen?
你们怎么才来?
Where the fuck you been?
-抱歉 -抱歉
-Sorry. -Sorry.
那是我所见过最性感的东西
That is the sexiest thing I've ever seen.
拉斯提  轮到你了
Rusty, you're up.
-你不接电话吗?  -我没带手机
-You gonna answer that? -I don't have a cell phone.
这不是我的
This isn't mine.
听听是谁的电话
See who it is.
-喂?  -能和本尼迪克特先生说句话吗?
-Hello? -May I have a word with Mr.Benedict?
是找你的
It's for you.
-是谁?  -有人在打劫你
-Who the hell is this? -The man who 's robbing you.
-金库怎么了?  -没事  先生  一切正常
-What's going on in the vault? -Nothing, sir. It's all normal.
给我看
Show me.
-恐怕你是错了 -看到你的监视仪了吗?
-You're mistaken. -Watching your monitors?
好好看着
Okay, keep watching.
在这城里  运气的变化实在是无常
In this town,luck can change that quickly.
-清点下那儿共有多少钱 -是  先生
-Find out how much money's down there. -Yes, sir.
泰丝?
Tess?
也许你应该...
Perhaps you should....
也许我应该什么?
Perhaps I should what?
这时候你离开这儿会好些
It would be better if you weren't around here for this.
好  你说的没错
All right, you proved your point.
你闯入了我的金库  恭喜你   现在你死定了
You broke into my vault. Congratulations. You're a dead man.
-也许是吧 -也许是吧? 恕我问你打算怎么离开?
-Maybe. -Maybe? May I ask how you will leave?
你以为我会让你带着钱 坦然走出赌场大门?
You think I'll let you take my money out my casino doors?
-不  你会帮我们搬出去的 -我为什么要这么做?
-No. You'll carry it out for us. -Why would I do that?
留意你的监视器
Look at your monitor.
也许你的经理已经向你汇报了   今晚存放在金库里
As your manager's probably reporting, you have over $160 million...
共有一亿六千万现金 我们只是拿走了一半
...in your vault tonight. We 're only packing up half that.
剩下的一半我们不拿走   就作为质物
The other half we 're leaving, booby-trapped, as a hostage.
若是让我们拿着这八千万走人 那我们会保全你的钱
You let our $80 million go,and you get to keep yours.
要是想阻止我们   我们就会把现金全毁掉
You try and stop us,we'll blow both cash loads.
你可以自行选择是失去 八千万或是失去一亿六千万
You can lose $80 million secretly or lose $160 million publicly.
做决定吧
Your decision. Hi.
快报警
Make the call.
911突发事件中心
911 emergency response.
-丹尼在哪儿?  -他很好  他在一个好地方
-Where's Danny? -He's fine. He's in good form.
-他要你起床后看电视 -他这么说的?
-He asks that you go up and watch TV. -He does?
这儿有三个人带着炸药   控制了金库
We have three men with explosives who have taken control of our vault.
-好吧 -没事的  泰丝
-Okay. -It's alright, Tess.
-条件接受 -我保证
-You have a deal. -I promise.
很好  现在你只需这么做
Fantastic. Here's what you do:
金库里的人会把六个包放在电梯里
The guys in the vault will put six bags in the elevator.
电梯会升至赌场
It will rise to your cages.
然后你的三个保安将包拿至赌场
Three of your guards will carry the bags out into the casino.
如果他们花的时间超过20秒   或是有什么变故发生
If they take more than 20 seconds to reach the floor, or there's a switch...
我们都会把钱毁掉
...we'll blow all the money.
-他在赌场通道口 -当然
-He's in the casino by the slots. -Of course I am.
我就住在你的酒店   送你个词: 迷你吧
I'm staying in your hotel. I have two words for you: mini bar.
等保安出了赌场
Once the guards hit the casino floor...
一辆白色货车会等在外面 你的保安就从后面装货
...a white van will pull up outside. Your guards will load the rear.
有任何人靠近驾驶室   我们就会把一切都炸掉
If anyone so much as approaches the driver's door, we'll blow everything.
等我听到货车离开  钱都安全了 我的人就会离开
When I hear the van is away and the money secure, my men will leave.
一旦他们安全得保   你的金库也就保住了
Once their safety is confirmed,you 'll get your vault.
特警队来了
The S. W. A. T. team is here.
好吧
All right.
我遵从你的一切要求 你满意吗?
Now, I have complied with your every request. Would you agree?
会满意的
I would.
很好  我还有句话要说
Good. Because nowI have one of my own:
躲的越远越好  混蛋!  躲的越远越好
Run and hide, asshole. Run and hide.
若是你在纽波特海滩 买下跑车招摇过市
If you're picked up buying a $100,000 sports car in Newport Beach...
...我会很失望的 我的人会找到你们
...l'll be disappointed. I want my people to find you, and when they do...
我们不会把你们交给警方
...rest assured, we won't hand you over to the police.
我再说遍我对你们的建议:  躲的越远越好
So, my advice to you againis this: run and hide.
我就只有这点要求
That is all that I ask.
本尼迪克特先生   我们的人说货车去了麦卡伦机场
Mr.Benedict, our guys say that van is headed for McCarran Airport.
在货车到达停机坪以前 我要我的金库安然无恙的回来
I want my vault back before that van hits the tarmac.
夜视仪已经打开   准备切掉电源
Night goggles on. Prepare to cut power.
准备
Ready.
现在切掉电源
Cutting power now.
快
Do it.
现在突破电梯门
Breaching elevator doors now.
发现两名不省人事的保安
We have two guards, bound, unconscious.
等等
Wait a minute.
兄弟们注意了!  有人来了!
Guys! Guys! Someone's here!
-把他干掉!  -得手了!
-Take him down, now! -I got him!
-开灯! 恢复供电!  -给他
-Lights! We need power now! -Give it to him.
怎么了? 告诉我
What's going on? Talk to me.
好象是炸弹被引爆了
It appears an explosive incendiary device has been detonated.
继续搜寻幸存者
Continuing search for survivors.
让他们拦住货车   我马上赶去那儿
Tell them to take the van. I'll be there.
问出他们是怎么破坏系统的!
And find out how they hooked into my system!
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
乖乖从车里出来!
Get out of the van, now. Now!
射轮胎
Tires. Tires.
我们搜查过了  没有嫌疑犯
Our search yielded no suspects.
我们也不能确认 他们是如何进入的
Nor can we determine how they entered or exited the premises.
-带你的人出去 -我能建议你...?
-Take your men out. -May I suggest you--?
快出去
Now.
这是你的金库 蓝队  离开这里!
It's your vault. Blue team, move it out!
威尔什  货车在哪儿?
Walsh, where are we with the van?
我还想再试会
I just want to try something for a second.
里面没有人
There's nobody inside.
-抱歉  你想要玩玩吗?  -玩够了吧?
-I'm sorry. Did you want to get in? -Enough monkey business.
快点干
Do it already.
本尼迪克特先生   我们控住了货车
Mr.Benedict. We took the van, sir.
然后呢?
And?
他们说车里没有钱  先生
They say there was nomoney in the bags, sir.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
他们说里面装满了都是卖淫传单
They say the bags were filled with fliers, sir. For hookers.
威尔什?
Walsh?
把录像倒回抢劫的那段
Cue up the tape to the robbery.
是的  先生  我正看着带子
Yes, sir. I'm looking at the tape now.
金库地板上有"美丽湖"字样吗?
Does it say "Bellagio "on the vault floor?
不  没有   这让我不明白了
No, it doesn't. I don't understand.
星期二我们刚加上去的
We had it installed Tuesday.
看来我们是让人用 事先录好的抢劫场面给胡弄了
The images we saw of those men robbing us was a tape.
什么?
What?
那都是假的   有人复制了我的金库
It was staged. Somebody made a duplicate of my vault.
监视器里的景象实际上并未发生
What we saw on the monitor wasn't actually happening.
我还是不明白  那么那些钱呢?
I don 't understand. What happened to all that money?
报警
Make the call.
911突发事件中心
911 emergency response.
-夜视仪已经打开 -收到
-Night goggles on. -Clear.
准备切掉电源
Prepare to cut power.
现在突破电梯门
Breaching elevator doors now.
发现两名不省人事的保安
We have two guards, bound, unconscious.
等等
Wait a minute.
兄弟们注意了!  有人来了!
Guys! Guys! Someone's here!
-把他干掉!  -得手了!
-Take him down, now! -I got him!
开门
Open the door.
本尼迪克特  外面 的拳击赛进行的怎么样了?
Hey, Benedict. How's the other fight going?
把他拉起来
Pick him up.
这事和你有关系吗?
Did you have a hand in this?
我和什么有关系?
Did I have my hand in what?
我再问你遍
I'll ask you one more time.
这事和你有关系吗?
Did you have your hand in this?
本尼迪克特   我不知道你在说什么
Benedict, I have no idea what you're talking about.
好吧
Okay.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
带他出去
Show him out.
-喂 -请转到88频道
-Hello. -Turn to channel 88.
是谁?
Who is this?
怎么了  本尼迪克特?  你被人抢了?
What happened, Benedict? You get robbed?
停下
Stop.
我最后给你次机会
I'll give you one last chance.
若我能归还你的钱
What ifl said you could get your money back...
而代价是你放弃泰丝
...if you 'd give up Tess?
你会如何选择?
What would you say?
我会说成交
I would say yes.
很好
All right.
我在监狱里认识个家伙
I know a guy. We were in the joint together.
任何人在西部犯事   他都了如指掌
Anybody pulls any job in the Western U. S. , he knows about it.
给我72小时   我会查出是谁偷了你的钱
Give me 72 hours, I'll find out who took your money.
你认识一个人
You know a guy.
联系警方  我想他 肯定违反了假释令
Contact the police. I'm sure he'sin violation of his parole.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
泰丝
Tess.
你手下所有人 都该知道  特瑞
You of all people should know, Terry.
在你的酒店里   总是有人在监视着
In your hotel,there's always someone watching.
等等!
Wait!
等等  那是我丈夫!
Wait, that's my husband!
-丹尼 -泰丝  我告诉过你...
-Danny. -Tess, I told you...
...我清楚自己在干什么
...l knew what I was doing.
我现在也明白了
I didn't.
好了  我们走吧
All right, let's go.
你会在里面呆多久?
How long will you be?
大约三到六个月吧
About three to six months, I guess.
三到六个月后
I hope you were the groom.
希望你就是新郎
Ted Nugent called, he wants his shirt back.
泰德纽吉特给过我电话 来要还他的衬衣
Thirteen million and you drive this piece of shit to pick me up?
一千三百万就换你这么来接我?
I blew it all on the suit.
我把那全花在买衣服上了
-Where are they? -Back row, silver sedan. Ten o'clock.
-他们在哪儿?  -后排  十点钟方向
I picked up your personal effects. Hope you don't mind.
我拿了你的私人财产   希望你不要介意
I'm not sure these belong to me.
我不知道那是否属于我
-Hi. -Hi.
拉斯提想要找个女孩
Rusty needs a girl.
沿着路走就有和女子监狱
There's a women's prison down the road.
你说早把戒指卖了
You said that you sold this.
我是这么说来着
I said that.
骗子
Liar.
贼
Thief.